blogadda.com 2007-12-29

# BlogAdda - Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy and User Agreement**

A user is subject to the Terms and Conditions policy of Blogadda.com. The Privacy Policy and User Agreement is effective from the date and time the user registers successfully with Blogadda.com by filling up the Registration form and accepting to the terms and conditions.

The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: [Blogadda.com](http://www.blogadda.com/ "Blogadda.com")

**Personal Information**  
In order to provide a personalized browsing experience, Blogadda.com may collect personal information from you. When you let us have your preferences, we will be able to deliver or allow you to access the most relevant information. Every effort will be made to keep the information provided by users in a safe manner.

The personal information provided by the users to Blogadda.com will not be provided to third parties without previous consent of the user concerned. Information of a general nature may however be revealed to certain external parties. Blogadda.com may use personal information about you to improve its marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze site usage, improve the site's content and product offerings, and customise the site's content, layout and services.

**Cookies**  
Blogadda.com may track the IP address of a user's computer and save certain information on your system in the form of cookies. A user has the option of accepting or declining the cookies of this website by changing the settings in your browser.

**Site Usage**  
A user always has the option of not providing the information which is not mandatory. You are solely responsible for maintaining confidentiality of your login details (username and password) and user identification and all activities and transmission performed by the User through his user identification. Blogadda.com assumes no responsibility or liability for improper use of user information.

**External Links**  
This site contains links to other sites. Blogadda.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

**Advertisers**  
We might use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies and we do not have access to this information.

**Contacting the Web Site**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can write to us.
